winkgo.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Winkgo

**On our site we collect the following:**

Email address

**Information is collected from you when you:**

Register on our site

**The information collected from you is used in the following ways:**

To personalize user’s experience

To improve the website

To improve customer service

To send periodic emails

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We use an SSL certificate

**We implement security measures when a user:**

**•** enters, submits, or accesses their information.

We use a payment gateway provider.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

**We use cookies to:**

**•** Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits,

It won’t affect the users experience

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

We use Google Adwords Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

**•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting

**We and third party vendors such as Google use:**

To compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

**•** On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

**•** By emailing us

**•** By logging in to their account

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

We do not allow

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under 13

**Fair Information Practices**

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email

**•** Within 7 business days

We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors

**CAN SPAM Act**

**We collect your email address:**

To send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

To market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to your clients after the original transaction has occured

**To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

We will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses

We will identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way

We will include the physical address of our business or site headquarters

We will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly

We will give an ‘opt-out’ or ‘unsubscribe’ option

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can**

**•** Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://winkgo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9dfef2f3e9fcfee9ddeaf4f3f6faf2b3fef2f0)

_Effective August 30, 2014_
